- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_01_Galahad_Resupply
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_01_Galahad_Resupply_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_Galahad_Resupply_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_01_Yash_RescueWarden
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_01_Yash_RescueWarden_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_Yash_RescueWarden_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_01_Judithe_RescueWarden
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_01_Judithe_RescueWarden_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_Judithe_RescueWarden_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_01_Pedro_RescueWarden
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_01_Pedro_RescueWarden_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_Pedro_RescueWarden_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_ThorpeNews
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_ThorpeNews_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_ThorpeNews_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_Tempest
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_Tempest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_03_Yonas_Tempest_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_05_Galahad_westoutpost
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_05_Galahad_westoutpost_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_05_Galahad_westoutpost_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_05_Yash_ExchangeInfo
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_05_Yash_ExchangeInfo_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_05_Yash_ExchangeInfo_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_07_Ofusa_RescuePortal
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_07_Ofusa_RescuePortal_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_07_Ofusa_RescuePortal_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_07_Jacquet_RescuePortal
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_07_Jacquet_RescuePortal_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_07_Jacquet_RescuePortal_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_07_Yash_Portal
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_07_Yash_Portal_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_07_Yash_Portal_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_09_Grace_Supplies
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Grace_Supplies_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Grace_Supplies_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_09_Yonas_Medicine
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Yonas_Medicine_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Yonas_Medicine_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_09_Yash_Medicine
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Yash_Medicine_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Yash_Medicine_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_10_Galahad_DefendCaerDun
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_10_Galahad_DefendCaerDun_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_MSQ_10_Galahad_DefendCaerDun_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 99D_MSQ_10_Yonas_CaerDun
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_Yonas_CaerDun_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@99D_Yonas_CaerDun_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
